Guide to the Deane W. Malott papers, 1951-1964
Malott, Deane W. papers, 1951-1964
- Board of Trustees - Executive Committee., 1955-56 (Box 18, Folder 55)
- Board of Trustees - Executive Committee. Class of 1916 Professorship., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 56)
- Board of Trustees - Executive Committee. Messing Bakeries, Inc.; Cornell Formula Bread., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 57)
- Board of Trustees - Executive Committee. Sibley School of Mechanical Engineering., 1955-56 (Box 18, Folder 58)
- Board of Trustees - Investment Committee. Harvard University., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 59)
- Board of Trustees - Buildings and Properties Committee., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 60)
- Cornell University Library Board. Olin Library., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 61)
- Olin Library., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  Hill, F. F.; McCarthy, Stephen A.; Metcalf, Keyes D.; Wood, Frederic C. Boardman Hall.
- Board on Physical Education and Athletics., 1956-57 (Box 18, Folder 63)
- College of Engineering Council., 1955-56 (Box 18, Folder 64)
- New York State College of Agriculture and the Agricultural Experiment Stations Council., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- New York State College of Home Economics Council., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- New York State Veterinary College Council., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Deans' Conference., 1957 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Atwood, Sanford S.
- Office of Public Information., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Williams, J. Robert; Knight, John S. "New York Times."
- Communism and Faculty Activities., 1955-56 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  Drummond, Burt; Taylor, Myron C.; Butler, Karl D.; Peterson, W. Fair field; Sokolsky, George F. Ithaca Reading Room Against Communism. Note: see Box 23 folder 35 for Communism, Faculty, 1954.
- Academic Freedom., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Philip Morrison., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Corson, Dale R. Morrison testimony in 1953 before the Internal Security Sub-Committee, Senate Judiciary Committee.
- Assistant to the President., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Walter A. Snickenberger., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Executive Assistant to the President. Elliott, Lloyd H., 1957 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Alumni Reports of the President., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  "Across the Years With Your Cornell" by DWM.
- Administrative Staff Meetings., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Office of the Provost., 1955-56 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  Hill, F. F.; Atwood, Sanford S. "What Size Cornell?" by Hill.
- Planning and Development., 1957 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  Gleason, James E.; Zwingle, J. L.; Morrison, Philip; Nixon, William V. 01 in Foundation; Cornell University Office of the Director of Development; Liberty Hyde Bailey Memorial Fund.
- Planning and Development., 1955-56 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  Nixon, William V.; Zwingle, J. L.
- Gifts., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 17-18)
- Gifts., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 19-21)
- Gifts., 1955-57 (Box 19, Folder 22-25)
- Reports on Gifts., 1955-57 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Greater Cornell Fund., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Cornell University Council., 1957 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Cornell University Council., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Cornell University Council., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Cornell University Council., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Parents weekend., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Cornell University Associates., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Vice President for Research., 1955-56 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Research Projects., 1957 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Vice President for Business., 1955-57 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Dept. of Buildings and Grounds., 1955-57 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Safety Division and Traffic Control., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Board on Traffic Control., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Barton Hall., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Residential Halls and Dormitories., 1957 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Purchasing Dept., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- College Stores., 1957 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Sage Chapel., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  "The Discipline of Loyalty" by DWM.
- Sage Chapel., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- Cornell University Airport., 1955-57 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  Underwood, E. Victor; Saperstone, David A. Mohawk Airlines.
- Office of the Treasurer., 1955-57 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  Herriman, Victor D.
- Academic Budgets., 1955-57 (Box 19, Folder 48)
- Office of the Director of the Budget. McKeegan, Paul L., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 49)
- Office of the University Counsel. Stamp, Neal R.; Meigs, Robert B., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 50)
- Tuition and Fees., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 51)
- Office of Admissions., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 52)
- Cornell Day., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 53)
- Office of the Registrar., 1954-55 (Box 19, Folder 54)
- Commencement., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 55)
- Cornell University Library., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  Wood, Frederic C.; Garber, Woodie; 01 in, John M. Olin Library; Cornell University Library Associates.
- Cornell University Library., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 57)
  Olin Library.
- Office of the Controller., 1955-57 (Box 19, Folder 58)
- Office of the Controller., 1955-56 (Box 19, Folder 59)
- Fraternities and Interfraternity Council. Weiss, Stephen H. Committee on Discrimination; Kappa Alpha., 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 60)
- Letters Regarding the Library., 1957 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  Clarke, Gilmore D.; Wood, Frederic C. Olin Library.
- Proposed Research Library (Olin Library)., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 62)
- Big Red Barn., 1957 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  Ball, William H.
- University Faculty., 1957 (Box 19, Folder 64)
- Committee on University Policy on University-Corporation Relationships., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 65)
- Prizes., 1953-54 (Box 19, Folder 66)
- Committee on Student Activities., 1955-56 (Box 19, Folder 67)
- Committee on Student Conduct., 1955-57 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  Wanderstock, J. J.; Phillips, Percy T.; Treman, Allan H.
- Undergraduate Scholarships., 1955-57 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  Committee on Undergraduate Scholarships.
- Laboratory of Ornithology., 1954-56 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
  Sherwood, Mary P.; Kellogg, Peter Paul; Swanson, Gustav A.; Alien, Arthur A.; Spofford, Sally Hoyt. An exhibit correspondence chronicling the accusations against Kellogg and Alien by the allegedly mentally unstable Sherwood.
- New York State College of Agriculture., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Myers, William I. University of the Philippines.
- New York State College of Agriculture Dept. of Extension Teaching and Information., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  Butts, George S.; Phillips, Elmer S.; Bond, Maurice C.
- College of Architecture., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  Will, Philip; Mackesey, Thomas W.; Detweiler, A. Henry; Singer, Marcus; Adelmann, Howard B.; O'Leary, Paul M. Communism.
- College of Arts and Sciences., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  Mineka, Francis E.; Black, Max; Rabinowitz, Isaac; Abrams, Meyer H.; Brown, Stuart M.; Caplan, Harry; Waage, F. O.; O'Leary, Paul M.; Hulse, M. L.
- Dept. of Chemistry., 1953-57 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  Manufacturing Chemists' Association.
- Dept. of Far Eastern Studies., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  Shadick, Harold; Oey, Giok Po; Sharp, Lauriston; Biggerstaff, Knight. Southeast Asia Program.
- Dept. of Mathematics., 1957 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  Walker, Robert J.
- Division of Modern Languages., 1957 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Dept. of Music., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  Sokol, Thomas A.; Grout, Donald J.; Kirkpatrick, John I.
- Band., 1955 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Chimes., 1955 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Sage Chapel Choir., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Dept. of Romance Literature., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Dept. of Physics., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  Corson, Dale R.; Smith, Lloyd P.
- Center for Training and Research in School Psychology (Proposed)., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Dept. of Sociology and Anthropology. Williams, Robin M., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- College of Engineering., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- School of Electrical Engineering., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Dept. of Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  Hollister, Solomon C.; Bard, F. N.
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Dept. of Engineering Physics., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  Smith, Lloyd P.; Bharadwaj, H. S.; Morrison, Philip.
- New York State College of Home Economics. Failing, Jean; Canoyer, Helen G. Housing Research Center., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- New York State College of Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; Humphreyville, Theresa., 1955-56 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Cornell University Medical College., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  Society of the New York Hospital.
- Cornell University Medical College., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  Luckey, E. Hugh; Douglas, Paul H.
- Cornell University Medical College., 1955-56 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  Correspondence with legislators re federal aid to medical schools.
- Cornell University Medical College -Transactions of the Executive Faculty., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- New York Hospital., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center Joint Administrative Board., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  Emanuel, Victor.
- Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 33-39)
- Cornell University Medical College Automotive Crash Injury Research Program. Cornell University Medical College Aviation Crash Injury Research Program., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Cornell Law School., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  Thoron, Gray.
- Cornell Law School., 1955-56 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  Dean, William Tucker; Pasley, Robert S.
- Cornell Law School - Dean Search List., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1955 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  Campbell, Ralph N.
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  Dunbar, Virginia M.
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  Sheppard, Charles Stewart; McEwen, William J.; Zwingle, J. L.; Litchfield, Edward H.
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1955-56 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  Litchfield, Edward H.; Schweitzer, Albert; Knowlton, Elizabeth R.; Canoyer, Helen G.; Corson, John J.
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration - Deanship., 1955-56 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  Francis, Clarence; Sheppard, Charles Stewart; Corson, John J.; Van Dusen, Albert C.; Mace, Myles L.
- School of Hotel Administration., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  Meek, Howard B.; Statler, Alice.
- Statler Club., 1955 (Box 20, Folder 50)
- School of Education., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 51)
- School of Nutrition., 1955 (Box 20, Folder 52)
- Graduate School., 1957 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  McConnell, John W.; Sherman, J. M. Association of Graduate Schools.
- Fellowships., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 54)
- ROTC, Dept. of Military Science and Tactics., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 55)
- Air ROTC., 1956 (Box 20, Folder 56)
- Oept. of Physical Education and Athletics., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 57)
- Army Reserve., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 58)
- Ivy League., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  Stevenson, William E.; Keeney, Barnaby C.; Harnwell, Gaylord P. Ivy Group Presidents Committee.
- Ivy League., 1954-57 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  Stevenson, William E.; Dodds, Harold W.
- Ivy League., 1953 (Box 20, Folder 61)
- Dept. of Physical Education for Women. Teagle, Walter C.; Kane, Robert J. Helen Newman Hall., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 62)
- NROTC., 1957 (Box 20, Folder 63)
- ROTC., 1955-56 (Box 20, Folder 64)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 65)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1955-56 (Box 20, Folder 66)
- Summer Session. Campbell, Ralph N., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 67)
- University Testing and Service Bureau., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 68)
- Cornell Plantations., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  Rockwell, George H.
- Infirmary and Clinic., 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  Moore, Norman S.; Gannett, Caroline Werner. Gannett Foundation.
- Cornell United Religious Work. Olds, Glenn A., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 71)
- Cornell United Religious Work. Olds, Glenn A. Danforth Foundation., 1957 (Box 20, Folder 72)
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 73)
- Cornell United Religious Work. Iran., 1955-56 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1955 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1957 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  Olds, Glenn A.
- Alumni., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Alumni. Zwingle, J. L. Class of 1916 Professorship., 1955-56 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Alumni Office., 1955-56 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  Bradley, Hunt; Colman, Charles C.; Kane, Robert J.; Brewer, R. Selden.
- Alumni Office., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Cornell Alumni News., 1957 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Scholarships., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Scholarships and Grants., 1956-57 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Scholarships and Grants., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 11-12)
- Scholarships and Grants., 1955-56 (Box 21, Folder 13-15)
- Sage Chapel Preachers., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Prizes., 1956-57 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Messenger Lectures., 1955-56 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  Tillich, Paul; Kirkland, Edward C.
- Division of Extramural Courses., 1957 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Fund for Adult Education., 1957 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Research Laboratory for Diseases of Dogs. American Kennel Club., 1955-57 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- State University of New York., 1955-56 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- William S. Carlson., 1953-56 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- New York State Education Dept., 1955-57 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  Fretwell, Elbert K.; Frodin, Reuben; Alien, James E.; Nyquist, Ewald B.
- New York State Education Dept., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- New York State Education Dept. - Degrees., 1955-57 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- New York State Education Dept. - Board of Regents., 1956-57 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  Morse, Frederick A.; Harriman, W. Averell.
- State University of New York Miscellaneous., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- State University of New York Miscellaneous., 1955-56 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- State University of New York - Conference on Higher Education., 1955 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- State University of New York - Board of Regents., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  Zwingle, J. L.; Hill, F. F.
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1959 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1958-59 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  Centennial Commemoration.
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1958 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  Thackrey, Russell I.; Jorgensen, Albert N.
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  Educational television.
- Association of American Universities. Kirkpatrick, John I., 1957-59 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Association of American Universities., 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York., 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  North, Thomas P. ACUSNY Commission on Non-Tax Supported Colleges and Universities, State of New York.
- Association of Universities of the British Commonwealth., 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- B Miscellaneous., 1957-59 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  Ball, William H.; Brewster, Frederick F. Bryant College; University of Buffalo.
- C Miscellaneous., 1957-59 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  Carpenter, Walter S.; Catchings, Waddill; Choue, Young Seek. Carnegie Corporation; Cayuga Lodge.
- Conferences., 1955-57 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Congressional Bills., 1958-59 (Box 21, Folder 43)
- Ezra Cornell 150th Anniversary Commemoration - Founder's Day., 1956-57 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  Harnwell, Gaylord P.; Bishop, Morris G.
- Corporate Aid to Higher Education., 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  Collyer, John L.; McCarthy, Charles W.
- Corson Report., 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  Cor son, John J. "A Memorandum on the Governing Cornell University."
- Cresap, McCormick and Paget., 1956-57 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  Survey of Administrative Management.
- D Miscellaneous., 1958 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  Dow Chemical Company.
- E Miscellaneous., 1958-59 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  Elliott, Lloyd H.; Elmhirst, Leonard K. Engineers' Council for Professional Development.
- F Miscellaneous., 1955-58 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  Ferry, Priscilla; Freeman, Harrop A.; Frost, Joseph N. Fund for the Advancement of Education.
- Ford Foundation., 1957-59 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  Borgmann, Carl W.; Corson, Dale R.
- G Miscellaneous., 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  Gannett, Caroline Werner; Gibson, Edwin T.; Zwingle, J. L.; Giles, Roscoe C.; Goodwillie, Edward E. Genesee Brewing Company.
- New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  Heinicke, Arthur J.; Myers, William I.; Luckett, J. D. 75th Anniversary of the Station.
- H Miscellaneous., 1957-59 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  Habein, Margaret. Hall of Fame for Great Americans; Committee on Government and Higher Education.
- United States Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare., 1957-59 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  Folsom, Marion B.
- I Miscellaneous., 1958-59 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  Keyes, H. M. R.; Watson, Thomas J. Institute Indigenista Peruano; International Association of Universities; IBM; International Cooperation Administration; International Educational Exchange Service.
- Ithaca, New York., 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 57)
- J Miscellaneous., 1959 (Box 21, Folder 58)
- K Miscellaneous., 1958-59 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  Kaufmann, Eugene M.
- L Miscellaneous., 1957-59 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  Rogers, William P.; Lewis, Fulton; Morrison, Philip; Orear, Jay; Konvitz, Milton R.; Lilienthal, Alfred M.; Lippmann, Walter. Lehigh Valley Railroad; Liberia.
- H Miscellaneous., 1958-59 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  Morrill, J. L.
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Stratton, Julius A.; Morrison, Philip; Killian, James R., 1955-58 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- N Miscellaneous., 1957-59 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  Nabokov, Vladimir; Nathan, George Jean; Needham, James G.; Neihardt, John G.; Noyes, Jansen.
- National Miscellaneous., 1957-59 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  National Industrial Conference Board; National League for Nursing; National Merit Scholarships.
- National Association of State Universities., 1958-59 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- National Commission on Accrediting. Selden, William K., 1957-58 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- P Miscellaneous., 1957-59 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  Paarlberg, Don; Paige, James W.; Pew, Joseph N. Princeton University.
- Q Miscellaneous., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  Queeny, Edgar M.
- Questionnaires., 1957-59 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- R Miscellaneous., 1957-58 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  Richards, Bartlett; Rogers, William P.; Rossiter, Clinton L. Rotary Foundation.
- Rockefeller Foundation., 1957-59 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  Kahin, George McT.
- S Miscellaneous., 1957-58 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  Schurman, George M.; Sale, William M.
- Seminar in Humanistic Studies., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Alfred P. Sloan Foundation., 1957-59 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  Zurcher, Arnold J.
- S Miscellaneous, 1956-58 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  Smith, T. V.; Stanton, Frank; Stevens, Robert T.; Sulzberger, Arthur Hays; Bailey, Liberty Hyde; Sweeney, Harold E.; Sweatt, Harold W. Student Demonstration, 1958.
- Spring Weekend 1957., 1955-57 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  Moore, Norman S.; Nowicki, Frederick J.; Humphreyville, Theresa; Kaufmann, Eugene M. Committee on Student Activities; Student deportment at parties.
- Spring Weekend 1957., 1957 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  Tobias, Richard; Freeman, Harrop A.; Hirshon, Louis M.
- Spring Weekend 1957., 1957 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  Woollen, J, Sellman; Lee, D. Boardman; Olds, Glenn A.; Christie, Edward L.; Opie, Ollie.
- Stained Glass Windows., 1956-58 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  Pike Stained Glass Studios.
- Student Demonstration, 1958., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Student Demonstration, 1958., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  Summerskill, John.
- Student Demonstration, 1958., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  Allport, Hamilton.
- Student Demonstration, 1958., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  Todd, Walter L.; Failing, Jean.
- Student Demonstration, 1958., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  Allport, Hamilton; Coffin, Foster M.; Newman, Floyd R.; Rockwell, George H.
- Student Demonstration, 1958., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  Beebee, Alexander M.; Beneway, Frank W.; Bull is, Gardner.
- Student Demonstration, 1958., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  Troy, Hugh.
- Student Demonstration, 1958., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  Grasselli, Caesar A.; Taussig, J. Wright.
- Student Demonstration, 1958. Kendrick, M. Slade; Will, Philip., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- student Demonstration, 1958., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  Talbott, John.
- Student Demonstration, 1958., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  Farina, Richard; Perry, Robert M.; Sale, J. Kirkpatrick; Seidler, David W.; Wheelwright, Peter W.
- T Miscellaneous., 1957-58 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  Talbott, John A.; Takagi, Sadaji; Taussig, J. Wright; Teagle, Walter C.; Tschirky, Leopold; Tuller, J. D.
- Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (TIAA)., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Teagle Foundation., 1958-59 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  Teagle, Walter C.
- Teagle Foundation., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Teagle Foundation., 1957-58 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- To Whom It May Concern Letters., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- U Miscellaneous., 1958-59 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  Wright, Theodore P. Massachusetts Institute of Technology; Union Carbide Corporation; United States Steel Corporation.
- V Miscellaneous., 1957-58 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  Blanding, Sarah Gibson. Commission on Non-Tax Supported Colleges and Universities.
- W Miscellaneous., 1957-59 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  Ward, J. Carl ton; Whiteside, Ruth Kinyon; Rockefeller, Winthrop. College of Engineering.
- XYZ Miscellaneous., 1957-58 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  Young, Philip.
- By- Laws of Cornell University., 1957-58 (Box 22, Folder 40-42)
- Board of Trustees - Random Notes Letters., 1957-58 (Box 22, Folder 43-44)
- Board of Trustees - Random Notes Letters., 1959 (Box 22, Folder 45)
- Board of Trustees., 1958-59 (Box 22, Folder 46)
- Board of Trustees., 1958-59 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  Collyer, John L.; Meigs, Robert B.
- Board of Trustees., 1957-59 (Box 22, Folder 48)
- Board of Trustees., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 49)
- Board of Trustees - Individual Members. Cornell, William Ezra; Of Connor, E. Jerome., 1957 (Box 22, Folder 50)
- Board of Trustees - Individual Members. Purcell, Robert W. Griff is, Stanton; Whitman, Ezra B., 1957-59 (Box 22, Folder 51)
- Board of Trustees - Ex Officio Members. McHugh, Keith S.; Wilson, Malcolm; Carey, Daniel J.; Dickinson, Edward T., 1958-59 (Box 22, Folder 52)
- Board of Trustees - John L. Collyer., 1958-59 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  Stephens, Thomas E. Olin Library; B. F. Goodrich Company.
- Board of Trustees - John L. Collyer. Student Demonstration, 1958., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 54)
- Board of Trustees - John L. Collyer. Student demonstrations; Collyer Boathouse., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 55)
- Board of Trustees - John L. Collyer., 1957 (Box 22, Folder 56)
- Board of Trustees - Frank S. Columbus., 1957-58 (Box 22, Folder 57)
- Board of Trustees - Arthur H. Dean., 1957-59 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  Summerskill, John; Clarke, Gilmore D.
- Board of Trustees - Mary H. Donlon., 1957-59 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  Fox, Edith M.
- Board of Trustees - Victor Emanuel. Healey, George H.; Hoover, J. Edgar; Carlson, William S., 1957-59 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Board of Trustees - Horace C. Flanigan., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Board of Trustees - Leroy R. Grumann., 1959 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Board of Trustees - Governor of the state of New York., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Harriman, W. Averell. Cornell University Library Regional History Collection.
- Board of Trustees - John S. Knight., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Board of Trustees - Larry E. Gubb., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Board of Trustees - Herbert F. Johnson., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Board of Trustees - Floyd R. Newman. Helen Newman Hall., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Board of Trustees - Nicholas H. Noyes. Noyes Lodge; Dept. of Rare Books., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Board of Trustees - John M. Olin., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Board of Trustees - Spencer T. Olin., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  Hollister Hall.